Franz Waxman Papers
Franz Waxman Papers
- Scores by Waxman
  - Demetrius and the Gladiators (Twentieth Century-Fox), 1954 (Oversize 32)
    Music cue sheets - Dec 8, 1953; Aug. 6, 1954
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) – original sketches
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) – originals and reproductions, some with annotations
    Restoration, "Gladiators' March" for concert band: including Instrumentation list, Full conductor's score - reproduction and Orchestral parts - reproductions, some with annotations
    Restoration, Suite: Orchestral parts - reproductions, some with annotations
  - Design for Scandal (M-G-M) (working title: "Miss Achilles' Heel"), 1941 (Oversize 33)
    Music cue sheet - Nov. 7, 1941
  - Destination Tokyo (Warner Bros.), 1944 (Oversize 34)
    Music cue sheet (2) - Dec. 31, 1943
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) - original sketches
    Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction with some annotations)
    Orchestral parts (Selections) - reproductions, some with annotations
    Selections - reproductions with annotations
    Re-orchestration of "Till We Meet Again" / arranged by by Franz Waxman
    "Destination Tokyo: a Montage for Orchestra" / arranged by by Christopher Palmer: Full conductor's score (Selections) - original and reproductions, Instrumentation list, Orchestral parts (Selections) - original, Holograph notes
  - The Devil Doll (M-G-M) (working title: "Witch of Timbuctoo"), 1936 (Oversize 35)
    Music cue sheet (partial) - Aug. 12, 1936
    Restoration for "Souvenir de Paris" waltzes by Christopher Palmer and Jeff Atmajian: Full conductor's score (Selections) - originals, Instrumentation list, Orchestral parts (Selections) - originals and reproductions, Holograph notes on instrumentation (photocopy), Notes (miscellaneous)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde (M-G-M), 1941 (Oversize 36)
    Music cue sheet - July 14, 1941
    Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction with additional copy of music cue sheet mounted on endpaper)
    Cinema Texas Program Notes - Nov. 18, 1974
  - Dramatic School (M-G-M), 1938 (Oversize 36.5)
    Music cue sheet - Dec. 3, 1938
  - Dusk: A Setting For Orchestra, See Night Unto Night (1949: Warner Bros.).
  - Edge of Darkness (Warner Bros.), 1943 (Oversize 37)
    Music cue sheet, undated
    Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction with annotations and with cast list mounted on endpaper)
  - Elegy for Strings, See Old Acquaintance (1943: Warner Bros.).
  - Elephant Walk (Paramount Pictures), 1954 (Oversize 38)
    See also Classic Film Themes Medley [III].
    Music cue sheet - Jan. 11, 1954
    Full conductor's scores (source material) - reproductions with annotations
  - The Emperor's Candlesticks (M-G-M), 1937 (Oversize 39)
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) (bound reproductions with music cue sheet mounted on endpaper and bearing date June 25, 1937)
  - Ernest Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man (Twentieth Century-Fox), 1962 (Oversize 40)
    Music cue sheet (3) - May 1, 1962
    Piano conductor's (Selections) - original sketches
    RCA Victor record album list of selections (photocopy)
    "Plaisir d'Amour" / Padre G. Martini "public domain" selection - reproduction
    Restoration for "Hemingway Suite": Full conductor's score (Selections) - originals and reproductions, Instrumentation lists (partial), Orchestral parts (Selections) - originals and reproductions
  - Escape (M-G-M), 1940 (Oversize 40.5)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 29, 1940
    Re-orchestration of "Preussen's Gloria" / arranged by by Franz Waxman
    Re-orchestration of "Wiener Blut" / arranged by by Franz Waxman
  - Ein' feste Burg ist unser Gott (Oversize 41)
    Piano score with annotations - original
  - The Feminine Touch (M-G-M), 1941 (Oversize 41.5)
    Music cue sheet - Aug. 30, 1941
  - Flight Command (M-G-M), 1940 (Oversize 41.7)
    Music cue sheet - Dec. 12, 1940
  - Florian (M-G-M), 1940
    - Suite for chamber orchestra, computer files; 12 .mus files
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 42)
      Music cue sheet (photostat) - Mar. 23, 1940
      Piano conductor's score (bound reproduction with copy of music cue sheet mounted on endpaper)
      Selection ("Ballet Suite for Miss Baronova") - reproduction
  - Four Scenes from Childhood (for violin and piano) "To Joseph Heifetz" (Oversize 43)
    Piano/violin score - reproduction with annotations
  - Franz Waxman Songbook (Oversize 43.5)
    Piano/vocal score - reproduction
  - Fur'n groschen Liebe/Ach, wie ist das Leben schon! (Berlin: Emelkaton-Verlag), circa 1932 (Oversize 44)
    See also Un Peu d'Amour.
  - The Furies (Paramount Pictures), 1950 (Oversize 45)
    Music cue sheet - Apr. 4, 1950
    Restoration for Suite: Instrumentation list, Full orchestral parts (Selections) - original and reproduction, some with annotations, and holograph notes on instrumentation (photocopy)
  - God Is My Co-Pilot (Warner Bros.), 1945 (Oversize 45.5)
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) (Bound reproduction with copy of music cue sheet mounted on endpaper)
    Conductor's score (Selections) - originals and reproductions
  - Goyana (), undated (Oversize 45.7)
    Full conductor's score - bound reproduction
  - Gruss und Kuss-Veronika (Deutsche Universal-Film A.G.), 1932 (Oversize 46)
    Selections (bound together) (Berlin: Alrobi Musikverlag, c1933): Gruss und Kuss-Veronika; Die kleinen Madchen mit dem treuen Blick
  - Gunsmoke (CBS Television Network), 1965 (Oversize 46.5)
    - "The Raid, Parts I & II":
      Music cue sheet (2) - Sept. 1, 1965
      Full conductor's score (Selections) - original sketches
      Holograph notes on music cues
  - He Ran All the Way (United Artists), 1951
    - He Ran All the Way, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 47A.1)
      A: Photocopied cue sheet (listing each scene name) used in the productions of He Ran All the Way (1951), produced by Roberts Productions, Inc., released by United Artists Corporation, 1 January 1951, and Flat Foot Fledgling (1951), produced by Terrytoons, Inc., released by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation, 29 October 1951.
      B: Conductor's score. Autograph (signed) Short score (pencil). Sections: Opening Fanfare ([1] leaf); Main Title (5 pp.); The Gun ([1] leaf); The holdup ([1] leaf); Peg comes home for lunch (2 pp.); The long night (5 pp.); Peg saves Nick (2 pp.); Final scene (5 pp.); End title and cast ([1] leaf); Rainy night ([1] leaf); The Dobbs meet the Killer (3 pp.).
    - He Ran All the Way, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 47A.2)
      A: (1) Reel 6 part 1. Violin, viola and horn parts. Transparency (black ink). (2) Reel 1 Part 2. Violin, viola and clarinet (1 & 2) parts. Transparency (black ink). (3) Main title. Full orchestra parts. Transparency (black ink). Also Reel 7 parts 1 & 2. Violin, viola, cello, bass, horn parts. Transparency (black ink). Also Reel 3 Part 2. Violin, viola parts. Transparency (black ink). (4) Reel 8 part 1. Final scene. Violin, viola, cello, horn parts. Transparency (black ink). (5) End title and cast. Violin, viola, cello, bass, horn parts. Transparency (black ink). (6) Reel 5 part 1. Violin, viola parts. Transparency (black ink).
      B: 1) Conductor's short score (mimeograph photocopied). Sections (in file order): End title and cast; Peg Saves Nick (7-1); The Gun (1-2); The Hold-up (1-4); Final scene (8-1); The long night (6-1); The Dobbs meet the killer (3-2); Peg comes home for lunch (5-1); Rainy Night (7-2). 2) Mimeograph sheets (mirror-image). Sections: The Gun; The Holdup; Rainy night; The Dobbs meet the killer; Maintitle; Peg saves Nick; The long night; End title and cast; Peg comes home for lunch.
    - He Ran All the Way, film score. Composed by Franz Waxman, arr. Leonid Raab. (Oversize 47A.3)
      A: (1) 3-1 Nick dances. Full score. Autograph (Raab?) (black & red ink) (16 + 1 pp.). (2) 3-1 Nick dances. Short score. Autograph (blue ink) (9 pp.). (3) Coda 1. Full score. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) ([1] leaf). (4) 1-1 Main title. Full score. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (15 pp.). (5) 1-4 The holdup. Full score. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (6 pp.). (6) 1-2 The Gun. Full score. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (2 pp.) (7) 5-1 Peg comes home for lunch. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (7 pp.) (8) 3-2 The Dobbs meet the killer. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (15 pp. (9) End title and cast. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (3 pp.). (10) 8-1 Final scene. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (21 pp.). (11) 7-1&2 Peg saves Nick. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (14 pp.). (12) 6-1. The long night. Autograph (Raab?) (pencil) (21 pp.).
    - He Ran All the Way, film score, parts. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 47B)
      A: Opening fanfare. Brass parts, autograph (black ink)
      B: Main title. Violin, viola, cello parts, mimeographed (with multiple copies)
      C: 1-2. Violin, viola, cello, bass, clarinet(1&2), horn parts, mimeographed (with multiple copies)
      D: 1-4. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
    - He Ran All the Way, film score, parts. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 47C)
      A: 3-1. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
      B: 3-2. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
      C: 6-1. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
    - He Ran All the Way, film score, parts. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 47D)
      A: End title and cast. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
      B: 8-1. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
      C: 7-1&2. Full orchestra parts, mimeographed (multiple copies)
  - Hemingway Suite, See Ernest Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man (1962: Twentieth Century-Fox).
  - Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man, See Ernest Hemingway's Adventures of a Young Man (1962: Twentieth Century-Fox).
  - Her Cardboard Lover (M-G-M) (working title: "Love Me Not"), 1942 (Oversize 48)
    Music cue sheet - May 20, 1942
  - Her Kind of Man (Warner Bros.), 1946 (Oversize 48.1)
    Music cue sheet - Feb. 28, 1946
    Orchestral part (Selection) - reproduction
  - His Brother's Wife (M-G-M), 1936 (Oversize 48.3)
    Music cue sheet - Aug. 13, 1936
    Piano conductor's Score (Selections) - reproductions
  - Home Before Dark (Warner Bros.), 1958 (Oversize 48.5)
    Music cue sheet - Oct. 29, 1958
  - Honky Tonk (M-G-M), 1941 (Oversize 48.7)
    Music cue sheet - Sept. 8, 1941
  - Honolulu (M-G-M), 1939 (Oversize 48.9)
    Music cue sheet - Feb. 4, 1939
  - The Horn Blows at Midnight (Warner Bros.), 1945 (Oversize 49, A-B)
    Music cue sheet - Apr. 19, 1945
    Piano conductor's score (Selections) - (bound reproduction with some annotations)
    Miscellaneous notes
  - Hotel Berlin (Warner Bros.), 1945 (Oversize 49.5)
    Music cue sheet - Mar. 12, 1945
    Miscellaneous notes on restoration
  - Humoresque (Warner Bros.), 1947
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 50)
      Music cue sheet - Sept. 30, 1946
      Carmen Fantasie: Full conductor's score - reproduction
      Carmen Fantasie: Full conductor's score - reproduction; Orchestral parts - reproductions
      Carmen Fantasie (New York: Harms, Inc., undated)
      Selection: P. Tschaikowsky Concerto (Opus 35) edited by Leopold Auer, adapted by Franz Waxman - reproduction
    - Miscellaneous, computer files; 20 .mus files
  - I Love You Again (M-G-M), 1940 (Oversize 50.5)
    Music cue sheet - Aug. 1, 1940
  - I, the Jury (United Artists), 1953 (Oversize 51)
    Music cue sheets - June 12, 1953 (2), undated
    Full conductor's score (Selections) - original
    Orchestral parts (Selections) - originals and reproductions with annotations
    "Molinero, Molinero" - "... p[ublic] d[omain] arranged by of Spanish folksong ..." - reproduction
    Miscellaneous production notes and financial material
  - Ice Follies of 1939 (M-G-M) (Oversize 51.5)
    Music cue sheet - Mar. 2, 1939
  - In Our Time (Warner Bros.), 1944
    - In Our Time, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 52A)
      A. Photocopied list of musical parts used in the production of In Our Time; lists each reel and number (uses different numbering system than in score), names of works in each medley of tunes, the works' composers, the publishers, the extent, how used and the length of time), 3 pp., 2 copies.
      B. (1) Conductor's short score of music for entire film (mimeographed, with markings in red pencil; (2) Reel 3 Part 2 from published piano score of Tchaikovsky's Swan Lake), bound.
    - In Our Time, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 52B)
      A. Another photocopy of list of musical parts (see 52A, item A).
      B. Folder labeled "'In Our Time,' music by Franz Waxman – Original Sketches." containing autograph (signed) draft short scores (pencil with markings and additions in red pencil) as follows:
      (1) Main title, 4 leaves; (2) Reel 1 Part 2, The Hunting Party, 5 leaves; (3) Reel 1 Part 3, Reel 2 Part 1, The Antique Shop; (4) Reel 2 Parts 2, 2A and 2B, Musical watch (Chopin Piano Concerto No, 1), 1 leaf, includes mimeographed short score for those same sections, 3 leaves; (5) Reel 2 Part 3, Invitation, 2 leaves; (6) Reel 2 Part 5, Opera house, 1 leaf; (7) Reel 3 Part 1A, [Chopin's] Les Sylphides, 2 p, includes 'Time' sheet ('tick' map) for Reel 4 Part 1, 2 pp, and mimeographed short score for Reel 3 Part 1A, 2 pp; (8) Reel 4 Part 4, Warsaw montage, 5 pp; (9) Reel 4 Part 4, Warsaw montage, by Waxman-Tedesco (with Mario Catelnuovo-Tedesco's signature on cover page), in Tedesco's hand (blue ink with markings in red pencil), at end: 'Mario, Beverly Hills, Oct, 16, 1943', 6 pp; (10) Reel 4 Part 5, Polish countryside, 4 leaves; (11) Reel 5 Part 1, Proposal, 4 leaves; (12) Reel 5 Part 5, Mother is shocked, 6 leaves; (13) Reel 6 Part 1, Uncle Pavel, 1 leaf; (14) Reel 6 Part 2, Jenny meets Pavel, 1 leaf; (15) Reel 7 Part 1, Back to Mrs Bromley, 2 leaves; (16) Reel 7 Part 2, The Railroad Station, 5 leaves; (17) Reel 8 Part 1, No more parties, 6 leaves; (18) Reel 8 Part 2, The new tractor, 1 leaf; (19) Reel 9 Part 1, Stephen is angry, Harvest Montage, by Waxman-Tedesco, in Tedesco's hand (blue ink with markings in red and black pencil), at end: 'Mario, Beverly Hills, Nov, 5, 1943', 11 pp; (20) Reel 10 Part 3, Warsaw bombing, 5 leaves; (21) Reel 11 Part 2, Reel 12 Part 1, Stephan comes home, 6 leaves; (22) Reel 12 Part 2, Finale, at end: 'Fine, Thank God!' 9 leaves; (23) Trailer, 5 leaves
  - The Indian Fighter (United Artists), 1955
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53A)
      A. Drafts of numbers in short and full score, as follows:
      (1) Reel 1 Part 2, Grey Wolf, autograph (initialled) full score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red pencil), 4 pp; (2) 'Theme from "Indian Fighter"', autograph (signed) full score (blue ink), 1 leaf; (3) 'Theme from "Indian Fighter" from the Bryna Production "Indian Fighter" starring Kirk Douglas (A United Artists Release)'. Lyrics by Irving Gordon. Music by Franz Waxman. Published vocal part (New York: Cromwell Music (mimeographed)), 1 leaf, 2 copies; (4) Reel 1 Part 1A, Main title (vocal), autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red pencil), 3 pp; (5) Reel 4 Part 1. frame click short score (black pencil with markings and additions in red and blue pencil), 20 pp; (6) Reel 2 Part 4, After the Fight, frame click ('bar breakdown') short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red, blue and black pencil), 10 leaves, 'To Franz Waxman, from Lloyd Young'; (7) Reel 7 Part 1, Grey Wolf Killed, frame click short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red, blue and black pencil and green ink). 6 pp; (8) Reel 8 Part 1, Attack on Fort, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red pencil; several insertions: black ink with markings in red and blue pencil), 10 pp; (9) Reel 5 Part 3, Looking for Johnny, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red pencil), 2 pp; (10) Reel 5 Part 3A, Love Scene, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red and blue pencil), 3 pp; (11) Reel 4 Part 2, The Photographer, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red pencil), 1 leaf; (12) Reel 6 Part 2, Second Love Scene, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red and green ink and red and blue pencil), 4 pp; (13) Reel 6 Part 2, Second Love Scene. Short score (black ink with markings in black pencil), 8 pp; (14) Reel 7 Part 3, Back to the Fort. Frame click short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red, blue and black pencil and red and green ink), 16 pp; (15) Reel 5 Part 2, The Wagon Train, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red ink and red pencil), 2 pp; (16) Reel 9 Part 1, Johnny's Escape, autograph (initialled) full score (blue ink with markings in red ink and red pencil, p. 4 has black ink with markings in red pencil), 4 pp; (17) Reel 9 Part 2, The Secret Place, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red pencil), 1 leaf; (18) Reel 10 Part 1, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red ink and red pencil), 1 leaf; (19) Reel 10 Part 2, Finale, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red ink and red pencil), 3 pp; (20) Repeat cast, 'Main title Bar 1-16', autograph short score (blue ink with markings in red pencil), 1 leaf; (21) Reel 3 Part 1, March, frame click short score ([no score is present] with markings in red, blue and black pencil), 14 leaves; (22) Reel 1 Part 1, Reel 10 Part 3 using coda, Main title (orchestral version), autograph short score (blue and black ink with markings and additions in red ink and red and black pencil), 3 pp; (23) Reel 1 Part 3, Johnny and Onahti, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings in red and green ink and red, black and blue pencil), 5 pp; (24) Reel 2 Part 2, No More Gold, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink), 3 pp; (25) Reel 2 Part 3, Fight with Grey Wolf, autograph (initialled) short score (blue ink with markings and additions in red ink and red and black pencil), 3 pp.
      B. Full score numbers (black pencil with markings in red and blue pencil), by Franz Waxman, arr. by Leonid Raab, as follows:
      (1) Reel 4 Part 1, 9 leaves; (2) Reel 1 Part 1A, Main Title (vocal), 12 leaves; (3) Reel 3 Part 1, Columbia The Gem of the Ocean, 6 leaves; (4) Reel 1 Part 3, Johnny and Ohnati, 5 leaves; (5) Reel 5 Part 3A, 12 leaves; (6) Reel 10 Part 1, 5 leaves; (7) Reel 4 Part 2, The Photographer, 3 leaves; (8) Reel 6 Part 2, 9 leaves; (9) Reel 2 Part 2, No More Gold, 10 leaves; (10) Reel 2 Part 4, 19 leaves; (11) Reel 7 Part 1, 12 leaves; (12) Reel 7 Part 3, 31 leaves; (13) Reel 8 Part 1, Attack on Fort, 42 leaves; (14) Reel 10 Part 2, Finale, 8 leaves; (15) Reel 2 Part 3, Fight with Grey Wolf, 9 leaves; (16) Reel 5 Part 2, The Wagon Train, 6 leaves; (17) Reel 10 Part 3, End Cast, 1 leaf; (18) Reel 1 Part 1, Reel 10 Part 3, Main Title (Instrumental), 10 leaves.
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53B)
      Photocopies of numbers of full score (originals in 53A-B except for Grey Wolf, which is in 53A-A), as follows:
      A. (1) Reel 1 Part 2, Grey Wolf; (2) Reel 1 Part 1A, Main Title (Vocal); (3) Reel 2 Part 4; (4) Reel 6 Part 2, Second Love Scene; (5) Reel 5 Part 3A, Love Scene.
      B. Reel 2 Part 4, full set of orchestral parts
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53C.1)
      A. (1) Reel 8 Part 1, Attack on Fort, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with pencil markings) and some mimeographed (with pencil markings); (2) Reel 8 Part 1A, full set of orchestral parts (only percussion) (mimeographed); (3) [Unidentified], 'A minor', draft (black pencil with markings in blue pencil), 1 leaf; (4) [Unidentified], 'March', 4 parts (black pencil with markings in red pencil), 1 leaf each.
      B. (1) Reel 9 Part 1, Johnny's Escape, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink) and some mimeographed; (2) Reel 9 Part 2, The Secret Place, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink) and some mimeographed; (3) Reel 10 Part 1, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with blue pencil markings) and some mimeographed; (4) Reel 10 Part 2, Finale, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black pencil markings) and some mimeographed with black pencil markings.
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53C.2)
      A. (1) Reel 7 Part 1, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black pencil markings) and some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (2) Reel 7 Part 3, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings) and some mimeographed (with black pencil markings).
      B. (1) Reel 5 Part 2, The Wagon Train, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (2) Reel 5 Part 3, Looking for Johnny, full set of orchestral parts, hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings); (3) Reel 5 Part 3A, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (4) Reel 6 Part 2, Second Love Scene, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings)
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53D.1)
      A. (1) Photocopied cue sheet, listing musical parts (listing the title of each number, its composer, the publisher, and the length of time), produced by Bryna Productions, Inc. and released by United Artists Corporation, November 18, 1955. 2 pp; (2) Reel 1 Part 1, Reel 10 Part 3, Main title (Instrumental) and Cast, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (3) Reel 1 Part 1A, Main title (vocal), full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (4) Reel 1 Part 3, Johnny and Onahti, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings)
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53D.2)
      A. (1) Reel 2 Part 2, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (2) Reel 2 Part 3, Fight with Grey Wolf, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings); (3) Reel 2 Part 4, full set of orchestral parts, some hand copied on manuscript paper (black ink with black and red pencil markings), some mimeographed (with black pencil markings)
    - The Indian Fighter, film score. Franz Waxman. (Oversize 53D.3)
      A. (1) Photocopied Instrumental breakdown sheet, listing for each musical part the length of time, the title, the reel and part numbers, the total number of parts, and the number of parts made for each instrument); (2) Orchestral parts [all numbers] for which more than one part is required, transparencies (black ink)